http://www.wolfandco.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Accounting, Tax, Audit and CPA Firm | Wolf & Company, P.C.
Last Update: April 7, 2017
Wolf & Company ("us", "we", or "our") operates https://www.wolfandco.com and http://lp.wolfandco.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection and Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. We collect certain personal information about you whenever you send an email to us or complete one of our online forms, such as the Contact Us form (https://www.wolfandco.com/contact-us). The personal information you provide can identify you and your business and may include, but is not limited to your name, email, company name, phone number, city, state, and ZIP code "Personal Information").
We also collect or log other information about you when you visit our website. This information includes your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and your domain name. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by the Internet Service Provider (“ISP”) computer through which you access the Internet, and a domain name is the name of the ISP computer itself through which you access the Internet.
We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party.
Log Data
We log IP addresses and domain names and aggregate them for system administration and to monitor the use of our website. We use the aggregated information, for example, to measure the number of visits to our website, the average time spent on our website, the number of pages viewed and to monitor various other website statistics.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, and other information that we believe will benefit you or your business.
If you do not wish to receive these communications from us, please unsubscribe by clicking here.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.
Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
Online Remarketing
We are a user of Google AdWords. We currently use the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise across the Internet. Wolf & Company complies with Google’s policy requirements.
Google AdWords remarketing service allows Wolf & Company to deliver relevant, online advertisements to targeted groups of anonymous users who have previously visited any Wolf & Company-owned and/or -managed website URL and/or app.
Using Google AdWords platform, Wolf & Company can deliver online banners, paid search ads, rich media ads, or other ad types across Google’s content network. This may include Google-owned properties as well as any non-Google-owned websites using the content network.
Neither Google AdWords nor Wolf & Company collects any personally identifiable information on any users without their expressed consent. All data collected by “cookies” are stored anonymously.
If you would prefer not to be remarketed by Google AdWords, you may opt-out at any time by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.
Social Media
Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the HubSpot’s Blog Social Sharing Icons button. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media buttons are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Third Party Tracking Technologies
We use HubSpot to help us analyze and understand Site traffic and user experiences. Some content that appears on this Site is hosted by HubSpot and may use cookies. HubSpot uses persistent cookies to recognize return visitors.  Read HubSpot's privacy policy here: http://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy.
Contact Wolf & Co
Ready to connect with a trusted advisor? Find office locations or submit an inquiry today.Contact Us
Events
November 13, 2020The Great New England Credit Union Show 2020Location: Sturbridge Host Hotel & Conference Center, Sturbridge, Massachusetts
SpeakingView event »
Insights
Survey Reveals Banks’ Increased Need for New Tech
U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission Makes Fundraising Easier
© 2020 Accounting, Tax, Audit and CPA Firm | Wolf & Company, P.C. All rights reserved.
99 High Street, Boston, MA 02110
(617) 439-9700
Website by Boston Interactive
